Guide to the Biographical Information on Yale University Affiliated Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Faculty vitae, press releases and clippings, 1972-1988; Accession 1991-A-038
  - Dubois, Rene, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 534)
  - Dumas, Rhetaugh (Nursing), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 535)
  - Eban, Aba, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 536)
  - Edelman, Marian, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 537)
  - Ervin, Sam, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 538)
  - Farber, Myron, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 539)
  - Fonda, Jane, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 540)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 541)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 542)
  - Ford, Gerald: Yale Law School Sesquicentennial Convocation Press Kit, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 543)
  - Ford, Gerald (Early Years), 1974-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 544)
  - Frank, Claude, undated (Box 5, Folder 545)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 546)
  - Friedan, Betty, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 547)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 548)
  - Gardner, C., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 549)
  - Geffen, David (Box 5, Folder 550)
  - Geller, Bruce, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 551)
  - Gibson, Kenneth, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 552)
  - Giersch, Herbert, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 553)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 554)
  - Glouster, Duke of, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 555)
  - Goldberger, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 556)
  - Gombrich, Ernst (Sir), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 557)
  - Grasso, Ella, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 558)
  - Greenfield, Meg, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 559)
  - Gruliow, Leo, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 559A)
  - Haggerty, Patrick, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 560)
  - Haig, Alexander, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 561)
  - Harper, Michael, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 562)
  - Harrington, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 563)
  - Harris, Louis, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 564)
  - Hawaiian Visitors, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 565)
  - Heaney, Seamus, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 566)
  - Heath, Edward, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 567)
  - Hernandez-Colon, Rafael, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 568)
  - Hills, Carla, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 569)
  - Hirshfeld, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 570)
  - Hnizdovsky, Jacques, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 571)
  - Hoagland, Jim, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 572)
  - Hsiao, Li-Sheng, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 573)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 574)
  - Hunt, E. Howard, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 575)
  - Ignatow, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 576)
  - India, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 577)
  - Iribarren, Ignacio, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 578)
  - Israel and Egypt: United Nations Ambassadors, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 579)
  - Italian Archaeologists, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 580)
  - Ivans, Michael (Box 6, Folder 581)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 582)
  - Jahn, Helmut, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 583)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 584)
  - Janeway, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 585)
  - Japanese Ambassador, undated (Box 6, Folder 586)
  - Jay, Peter (British Ambassador to United States), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 587)
  - Jenner, Bruce, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 588)
  - Jordan, Vernon, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 589)
  - Kantorovich, Leonid, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 590)
  - Kassebaum, Nancy, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 591)
  - Kaye, Danny, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 592)
  - Keele, Kenneth, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 593)
  - Kelly, Clarence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 594)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 595)
  - Kennedy, Edward, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 596)
  - Kennedy, Johnf. (Box 6, Folder 596A)
  - Kingsley, Nathan, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 597)
  - Koch, Edward I., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 598)
  - Koh, T. T. b., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 599)
  - Koirold, b. P., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 600)
  - Kolesov, Vladimir V., undated (Box 6, Folder 601)
  - Kornberg, Arthur, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 602)
  - Kroc, Ray A., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 603)
  - Kung, Hans, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 604)
  - Kung, Hans, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 605)
  - Ky, Nguyen Cao, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 606)
  - Lacan, Jacques, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 607)
  - Lapham, Louis, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 608)
  - Le Boyer, Frederick, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 609)
  - Levi, Edward, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 610)
  - Lin, Ma, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 611)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A. (Box 6, Folder 612)
  - Lindsay, John, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 613)
  - Linsky, Martin, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 614)
  - Lipshutz, Robert, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 615)
  - Lothian, Lord, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 616)
  - MacDonald, Dwight, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 617)
  - Mack, John E., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 618)
  - MacMillan, Harold, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 619)
  - MacNeil, Robert, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 620)
  - Mainland Chinese Physicists, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 621)
  - Marchand, Len, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 622)
  - Mathias, "Mac", undated (Box 6, Folder 623)
  - Mauksh, Ingeborg G., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 624)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 625)
  - Meier, Richard A., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 626)
  - Merril, James, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 627)
  - Merwin, W. S., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 628)
  - Michaels, Lorne, undated (Box 6, Folder 629)
  - Michener, James, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 630)
  - Miller, G. William, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 631)
  - Mitchell, Parren, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 632)
  - Mondale, Joan, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 633)
  - Mondale, Walter, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 634)
  - Mooney, Dick, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 635)
  - Motley, Constance b., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 636)
  - Moynihan, Patrick, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 637)
  - Mulhauser, Karen, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 638)
  - Napolitano, Giorgio, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 639)
  - Neizvestny, Ernst, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 640)
  - Neubauer, Peter, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 641)
  - Neuman, Edwin, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 642)
  - New Haven High School Day at Yale, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 643)
  - Newman, Paul (Box 6, Folder 644)
  - Newman, Paul, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 645)
  - Panama Canal Treaty, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 646)
  - Parker, Roberta, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 647)
  - Patterson, Carolyn b., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 648)
  - Paz, Octavio, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 649)
  - Peace Corps, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 650)
  - Percy, Charles H., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 651)
  - Pierpoint, Robert, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 652)
  - Porter, Sylvia, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 653)
  - Powell, James, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 654)
  - Proxmire, William, undated (Box 6, Folder 655)
  - Rather, Dan, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 656)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1967, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 657)
  - Redford, Robert, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 658)
  - Reed, Ishmael, undated (Box 6, Folder 659)
  - Reed, Ola Belle, 1975-78 (Box 6, Folder 660)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 661)
  - Rich, Adrienne, undated (Box 6, Folder 662)
  - Richardson, Elliot, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 663)
  - Roberts, Walter Orr, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 664)
  - Rooney, Andrew, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 665)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 666)
  - Rusher, William, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 667)
  - Rusk, Dean, undated (Box 6, Folder 668)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 669)
  - Salah, Abdullah, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 670)
  - Salisbury, Harrison, undated (Box 6, Folder 671)
  - Saunders, Gerd, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 672)
  - Schell, Maximilian, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 673)
  - Schlessinger, James, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 674)
  - Schmidt, Helmut, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 675)
  - Schorr, Daniel (Box 6, Folder 676)
  - Shapiro, Irving, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 677)
  - Shapiro, Miriam, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 678)
  - Sharansky, Natan, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 679)
  - Shields, Nelson, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 680)
  - Shockley, William, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 681)
  - Simon, Paul, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 682)
  - Smith, Hedrick, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 683)
  - Soares, Mario, 1976? (Box 6, Folder 684)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexsandr, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 685)
  - Spitzer, Lyman, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 686)
  - Spock, Benjamin J., 1980-85 (Box 6, Folder 687)
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 688)
  - Steinsaltz, Adin, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 689)
  - Stewart, Potter, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 690)
  - Stewart, Slam, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 691)
  - Strauss, Robert, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 692)
  - Sullivan, Scott, undated (Box 6, Folder 693)
  - Sullivan, Walters, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 694)
  - Thomas, Lewis, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 694A)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 695)
  - Todd, Garfield, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 696)
  - Tramczynski, Witold, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 697)
  - Trudeau, Garry, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 698)
  - Turner, Stansfield, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 699)
  - Verdy, Violette, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 700)
  - Villa-Lobos, Aminda, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 701)
  - Warnke, Paul, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 702)
  - Waterson, Samuel, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 703)
  - Walpole, Horace, undated (Box 7, Folder 704)
  - Weaver, Robert C., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 705)
  - Wilkins, Roy, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 706)
  - Winship, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 707)
  - Wolfe, William, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 708)
  - Woods, Donald, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 709)
  - Wriston, Walter, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 710)
  - Weicker, Lowell, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 711)
  - Wells Fellowship, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 712)
  - Wednesday Club, 1975-79 (Box 7, Folder 713)
  - Whiffenpoofs--General, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 714)
  - Whiffenpoofs--70th Anniversary, 1975-79 (Box 7, Folder 715)
  - Whitney Humanities Center: Yale Journal of Criticism, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 716)
  - Women and Yale: Transitions, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 717)
  - Women"s Center, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 718)
  - Women Faculty, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 719)
  - Women"s Forum "76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 720)
  - Writing Program, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 721)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine--Book Jackets, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 722)
  - Yale Arms Description, undated (Box 7, Folder 723)
  - Yale Aviation, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 724)
  - Yale Band, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 725)
  - Yale Band--Richard Thurston, Director, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 726)
  - Yale Band, undated (Box 7, Folder 727)
  - Yale Bowl: Charity, 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 728)
  - Yale Broadcasting Company, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 729)
  - Yale Broadcasting Company, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 730)
  - Yale Cabaret, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 731)
  - Alumni Reunions
    - Class of 1945W, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 732)
    - Class of 1929, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 733)
    - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 734)
    - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 735)
    - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 736)
    - Officers" Meeting, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 738)
    - Class of 1943, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 739)
    - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 740)
    - Class of 1934, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 741)
    - Class of 1934, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 742)
    - Class of 1929, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 743)
    - Class of 1929, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 744)
    - Class of 1959, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 745)
    - Class of 1940, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 746)
    - Class of 1954, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 747)
    - All Classes, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 748)
    - Class of 1945W, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 749)
    - Class of 1920, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 750)
    - Class of 1925-25s, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 751)
    - Class of 1929--A. b. Giamatti, Hon. Member, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 752)
    - Class of 1930, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 753)
    - Alumni Reunions, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 754)
    - Class of 1935, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 755)
    - Class of 1949, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 756)
    - Class of 1935, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 757)
    - Class of 1955, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 758)
    - President"s Reception: Alumni Weekend, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 759)
    - Class of 1931, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 760)
    - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 761)
    - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 762)
    - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 763)
    - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 764)
    - 1978 (Box 8, Folder 765)
    - 1978 (Box 8, Folder 766)
    - 1980 (Box 8, Folder 767)
    - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 768)
    - 1980 (Box 8, Folder 769-770)
- Biographical information on Yale University faculty, circa 1938-1990; Accession 1995-A-033
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Adams, Brent L. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alderfer, Clayton P. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alderman, Donald, M.D. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alevy, Daniel I. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Elizabeth C. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amara, Susan G. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Marston (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ariyan, Stephen (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Astrachan, Boris M. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Auld, Louis E. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Axelrod, Robert (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Baker, Joyce K. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bapat, Dr Vijaya (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Barghoorn, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barnhart, Richard M. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barrnett, Russell, M.D. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Barten, Paul K. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barthold, Stephen W. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Barwick, Kenneth W. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Basso, Keith H. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Battin, Carol M. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Baugh, William J. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Baumer, Franklin L. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bergin, Thomas G. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Berglund, Larry G. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Berlowe, Max L., M.D. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bernard, Gary D. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Berneike, Robert R., M.D. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bernucci, Leopolodo M. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bertino, Joseph R. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bewell, Alan J. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Binkley, Clark S. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Birchette, Mark G., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Blanshard, Brand (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bonito, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Boone, Sylvia (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bork, Robert H. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Boxer, Charles R. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Boyden, James M. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Brandenburg, Judith B. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brewer, Gary D. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bricker, Phillip (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Brilmeyer, Lea (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Broadie, Sarah W. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Brochin, Malcolm, M.D. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Brosious, Ed (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Brown, Donald J. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Brownell, Samuel (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Brownstein, Oscar (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Brubacher, John S. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Brueckner, Anthony (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Brunbaugh, Robert (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Brusati, Celeste A. (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Brusic, Robert (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Brustein, Robert (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Buckman, John W. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Buxton, Claude E. (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Cambell, Roger L. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Cappiello, Louis (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Carter, Max G. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Cashmore, Roger J. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Chamley, Christopher (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Chang, Pauline W.K. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Chao, Howard S. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Chaplin, Hamako (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Chen, Lung Chu (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Chen, Marina C. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Chermayeff, Serge (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Chrisman, O.D. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Clarke, James G. (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Clausing, Stephen (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Clement, David, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - CoFancesco, Dal (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Coleman, Jules V. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Collins, John G. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Colson, Steven D. (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Connolly, Arthur (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Cook, John W. (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Cooke, Michael G. (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Cooper, Peter S. (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Copland, M. Shawn, O.P. (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Cormack, Malcolm (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Cory, Eleanor (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Cotlier, Edward, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Cramton, Peter C. (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Cronon, William J. (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Curran, Mark (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Curtis, C. Martin (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Da Costa, Gary S. (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Daly, Kathleen (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Dane, Perry (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Daniels, Lois K. (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Danishefsky, Sarah E. (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Davis, Charles T. (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - DeCherney, Alan H. (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Dees, J. Gregory (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - DeFronzo, Ralph A. (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Dellarosa, Denise (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Denardo, Eric V. (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Denison, Geroge A., Capt. (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - D"Eramo, Gail A. (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - DeRose, David J. (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Derrida, Jacques (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Diaz-Alejandro, Carlos (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Di leonardo, Micaela (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Dilkes, Katy (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - DiMaggio, Paul J. (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Dineen, Joseph P. (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Dobihal, Edward, Jr., Rev. (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Donaldson, Robert, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Downs, Wilbur G., M.D. (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Dreyfus, Laurence (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Duff, Raymond S., M.D. (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Dybvig, Philip H. (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Ellis, David B. (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - El Rassi, Ziad (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Embersits, John F. (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Emerson, Thomas I. (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Estabrook, Henry W. (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Eyler, Edward E. (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Farquhar, Marilyn (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Fasanella, Rocko, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Fassler, Margot E. (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Fehr, Edith B. (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Felig, Philip, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Ferholt, Judith D. (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Ferrari, Giovanni R.F. (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Field, Robert J., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Field, William W., M.D. (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Fillin-Yeh, Susan (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Findlay, John N. (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Finley, Lucinda M. (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Fischer, John (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Fitch, Frederic B. (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Flynn, Kathleen T. (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Forbes, Thomas R., M.D. (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Forsberg, Joan B. (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Frank, Claude (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Frankel, Saul, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Frankfurt, Harry (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Freedman, Jonathan (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Frei, Hans W. (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Froula, Christine (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Fuller, Janet, Rev. (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Fuoss, Raymond M. (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Futterman, Edward, M.D. (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Gage, Charles S. (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Gallagher, J. Roswell, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Gambrill, Bessie (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - Gardner, William, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Gardner, Richard K. (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Gatzke, Hans W. (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Gehry, Frank O. (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Gibson, Ann Eden (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Gilbert, Joan A. (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Gindroz, Raymond (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Glass, William (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Goff, William R. (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Goldsmith, Raymond (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Goldstein, Jakub (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Goodkin, Richard E. (Box 3, Folder 161)
  - Goody, Jack G. (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Gottschalk, Alexander, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Greenberg, Stanley B. (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Griffin, Martin L. (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - Gropp, William D. (Box 3, Folder 166)
  - Gryboski, Joyce M.D. (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - Guillory, John David (Box 3, Folder 168)
  - Gursey, Feza (Box 3, Folder 169)
  - Hadley, Nicholas JohnÂ (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Haight, Charles J. (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - Hait, William (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - Hakuta, Kenji (Box 3, Folder 173)
  - John, Hardin A. (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - Harvey, Henry H. (Box 3, Folder 175)
  - Harvey, Richard R. (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Hathaway, John, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Hauslohner, Peter (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Havelock, Eric (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Heckman, James (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Hedlund, Gustav A. (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Henning, Basil D. (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Herbert, Robert L. (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Herrman, Eleanor K. (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Herrup, Karl (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Hexter, Ralph J. (Box 3, Folder 186)
  - Hickey, Mairead (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Hobbins, John C. (Box 3, Folder 188)
  - Hodapp, Robert M. (Box 3, Folder 189)
  - Hotcomb, Wade G. (Box 3, Folder 190)
  - Holland, Lane M. (Box 3, Folder 191)
  - Holmberg, Sharon K. (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Honegger, Gitta S. (Box 3, Folder 193)
  - Howard-Flanders, Paul M.D. (Box 3, Folder 194)
  - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn (Box 3, Folder 195)
  - Hyde, Martha M. (Box 3, Folder 196)
  - Hyde, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - Ihaka, G. Ross (Box 3, Folder 198)
  - Immerman, Neil (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Insdorf, Annette (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Izenour, George (Box 3, Folder 201)
  - Jacobson, Susana V. (Box 3, Folder 202)
  - Jacoby, Alberta Smith (Box 3, Folder 203)
  - James, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 204)
  - Janerich, Dwight T. (Box 3, Folder 205)
  - Janis, Irving L. (Box 3, Folder 206)
  - Jensen, Roderick V. (Box 3, Folder 207)
  - Johnson, Edward C. (Box 3, Folder 208)
  - Johnson, Lester (Box 3, Folder 209)
  - Johnson, Mary Alice (Box 3, Folder 210)
  - Johnsson, Lennart (Box 3, Folder 211)
  - Jones, William (Box 3, Folder 212)
  - Joplin, Patricia K. (Box 3, Folder 213)
  - Kahn, Herman (Box 3, Folder 214)
  - Kantor, Paul (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - Karachuk, Halina L. (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - Leon, Katz (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Kauer, John S. (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Keith, Howard D. (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Kellar, Deane (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Kenefick, J. Gordon (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Kessler, Friedrich (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Keul, Norman Carl (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Kier, Eliezer, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Kieber, Herbert (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Kletzer, Kenneth M. (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Koditschek, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Koniak, Susan P. (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Kraakman, Reinier (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Kramemer, Deborah Tebes (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Krantz, James (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Krauss, Lawrence M. (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Kabovy, Miri (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Kammer, Alfred J. (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Kupferberg, Audrey (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Labs, Kenneth B. (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Lach, Frank E. (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Lande, Saul (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Lang, Dr. Robert (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Lansberg, Ivan (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Lattanzi, William E. (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Leaf, Phillip J. (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Lee, Hong Yung (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Lee, Jonathan (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Leers, Andrea P. (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Lennard, Wolfgang (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - Leung, Janny (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Levinson, Herbert S. (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - Lewandowski, Linda Ann (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - Lewin, Frank (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Lillian, Marvin, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Linfield, Eva (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Lisansky, Milton (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Loewald, Hans, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Loftus, R. Charley (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Longhi, John (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Lowman, Robert K., M.D (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Lull, David J. (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Lumelsky, Vladimir J. (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - Lutz, Harold J. (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Lutz, Nancy A. (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Lyons, Williams P. (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - McCluggage, Nancy Anne Ford (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Mcgerr, Rosemarie P. (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - McGregor, Deborah, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - McGinnis, William (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - McGuire, Joseph, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - McKivigan, John R. (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - McLellan, Robert K. (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - McLennan, Gloria J. (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - McMullan, Frank (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Macrae-Gibson, Gavin (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Malkiel, Burton G. (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Manuelidis, Elias, M.D. (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Marr, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Marshall, Vanesa A. (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Massey, Walter E. (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Matzke, Martha K. (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Matzkin, Rosa L. (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Mergin, Francois (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - Meschede, Dieter (Box 4, Folder 281)
  - Mesquita, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Mezias, Stephen J. (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Michael, Charles R. (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - Migdalski, Edward (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Miller, Harold (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Miller, J. Hillis (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - Milnes, Sherrill (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Mitchell, Alphonsus (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Mochizuki, Mike M. (Box 4, Folder 290)
  - Molde, Susan L. (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - Molloy, Sylvia (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Moore, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - Moore, Leslie E. (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - Moorthy, K. Sridhar (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Morgenthaler, Stephan (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - Moriarty, Phillip E. (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Morowitz, Harold (Box 4, Folder 298)